<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Portfolio on CARIN Thomas</title>
    <link>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project Portfolio on CARIN Thomas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project IV : Masked recognition AI</title>
      <link>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>In this school project, we are a team of 5 students, and we are challenged to program an AI that will understand thanks to a photo if a human is wearing a safety mask or not, but also if this safety mask is well-worn
This project will help me discover Neural Networks, and Computer Vision.
There is not much content now, because we just started the project. But I will update this project page during the project, so stay in touch !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project III : Dots and Boxes AI</title>
      <link>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>In this school project, we have to program an AI playing the game Dots and Boxes. Our AI will be evaluated in a tournament where all the AI of the class are attending.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently programming a handmade algorithm, and after that I will train a Reinforcement Learning AI against my algorithm.
There is not much content now, because I just started the project. But I will update this project page during the project, so stay in touch !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project II : Web application for patients&#39; reconditioning after surgery</title>
      <link>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>In this personal project, I developed a web application that help patients that had surgery to recover. They can do physical and psychosocial exercises to maintain a physical condition and keep their brain active.
This project is private, the code isn&amp;rsquo;t accessible. But I had the autorization to do a little demo in video :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project I : Tennis Prediction</title>
      <link>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>This is my first project in Data Science. I&amp;rsquo;m a fan of tennis, after practicing during 7 years. I missed the court. What could be more interesting than studying Data Science with a little bit of nostalgia. We tried to answer : Can tennis outcomes be predicted thanks to data available on the internet ?
I did this project with a friend of mine : Florian DECONINCK, we had 3 weeks to do the analysis and create a dashboard on a website to see latest tweets regarding tennis, see different results of tennis matches and link our predictions to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thrynk.github.io/Portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you think I can be a valuable asset for your company or have some insight for my projects.
I would love to talk more with you, you can contact me on :
   Plateform : Link     LinkedIn : https://www.linkedin.com/in/thomas-carin-843691151/   Email : thomas.carin@isen.yncrea.fr    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
